Broadcast Center Recordings, circa 1980-2017: Finding Aid AC362
University Archives
- Series 8: Broadcast Center Recordings, 2015 October 2-2017 July 20; 228 digital files
  - Simons Collaboration Workshop on Numerical Bootstrap, 2017 March 01; Princeton University. Department of Physics; 1 digital file (Item 3614D)
    Details: Simons Collaboration Workshop on Numerical Bootstrap Wednesday, March 1 9:30 am\tCoffee and Continental Breakfast 10:00 am\tAndreas Stergiou | \Mixed correlator 4D N=1 superconformal bootstrap\ 11:15 am\tSimon Caron-Huot | \Analyticity in spin and an inverse operator product expansion\ 12:15 pm\tLunch 2:00 pm\tDenis Karateev | \Bootstrap Equations of Arbitrary Spin Representations in 4D CFTs\ 3:00 pm\tCoffee and Sweets Thursday, March 2 9:30 am\tCoffee and Continental Breakfast 10:00 am\tShai Chester | \Monopole operators in U(1) Chern-Simons theories\ 11:15 am\tMadalena Lemos | \The 4d N=3 bootstrap and 2d long blocks\ 12:15 pm\tLunch 2:00 pm\tXi Yin | \Bootstrapping the spectral function\ 3:00 pm Coffee and Sweets 3:15 pm\tAlessandro Vichi | \Update on the four current bootstrap\ 6:00 pm\tDinner | Triumph Brewing Company Friday, March 3 9:30 am\tCoffee and Continental Breakfast 10:00 am\tFernando Alday | \Large spin perturbation theory\ 11:15 am\tAgnese Bissi | \Loops in AdS from CFT\ 12:15 pm\tLunch 2:00 pm\tPetr Kravchuk | \Representation-theoretic approach to tensor structures and the Casimir equation\ 3:00 pm\tCoffee and Sweets
  - PIIRS GSR Lecture: \The Architecture of Collapse: The Global System in the 21st Century\, 2016 December 07; PII-Prin Inst Intl-Reg Stud; 1 digital file (Item 3615D)
    Speakers:Mauro Guillen (UPenn), Simon Levin (Princeton EEB); Details: Wednesday, December 7, 2016 The Architecture of Collapse: The Global System in the 21st Century Mauro Guillen, Director of Joseph A. Lauder Institute at U. Pennsylvania, Dr. Felix Zandman Professor of International Management, Wharton School, Professor of Sociology, U. Pennsylvania 4:30pm, Guyot Hall, Room 10; Run Time: 01:16:20:15
  - Academic Tribute in Honor of Laura Landweber, 2016 December 02; EEB-Administration; 1 digital file (Item 3616D)
    Speakers:Han Liang, Aaron Goldman, Rob Knight, Mariusz Nowacki, Estienne Swart, Naomi Stover, Ed Curtis, Adam Ruben
  - Synthesia of Law (Day Two), 2016 September 30; GER-German; 1 digital file (Item 3617D)
  - AAS Graduate Conference, 2017 April 20; Princeton University. Center for African American Studies; 1 digital file (Item 3618D)
  - SICSS 2017, 2017 June 21; USV-CES-Representative 6; 1 digital file (Item 3619D)
  - Saudi Arabia and Iran: Building Understanding for Improved Ties, 2016 October 26; MRC-Mossavar-Rahmani Center; 1 digital file (Item 3620D)
    Speakers:Banafsheh Keynoush & Cyrus Schayegh; Details: http://www.princeton.edu/iran/events/; Run Time: 53:39:00
  - Dean's Lecture Series: Antoine Picon, 2016 October 27; Princeton university. School of architecture; 1 digital file (Item 3621D)
    Speakers:Antoine Picon; Details: Dean's Lecture Series: Antoine Picon; Run Time: 1:35:02
  - Architecture Open House: Thom Mayne, 2016 November 07; Princeton university. School of architecture; 1 digital file (Item 3622D)
    Speakers:Thom Mayne; Details: Dean's Lecture Series: Thom Mayne; Run Time: 2:01:36
  - Campus Iconography, 2016 November 09; EVP-Executive Vice President; 1 digital file (Item 3623D)
    Speakers:Andy Chen '09 and Waqas Jawaid '10; Details: http://evp.princeton.edu/committees-and-initiatives/campus-iconography/november-9-2016-public-lecture; Run Time: 1:06:30
  - Politics Plenary Sessions (Fall 2016), 2016 November 11; Princeton University. Department of Politics; 1 digital file (Item 3624D)
    Speakers:Professors Nolan McCarty & Alisha Holland; Details: Politics juniors are required to attend the Plenary Sessions. We plan to make the recordings available only to the students who will be studying abroad.; Run Time: 1:41:49
  - Stew Smith Retirement Symposium, 2016 November 12; Princeton University. Department of Physics; 1 digital file (Item 3625D)
    Run Time: 5:03:41
  - A Conversation with Deborah Kass, 2016 November 14; HUM-American Studies; 1 digital file (Item 3626D)
    Speakers:Deborah Kass, Stacy Wolf, Esther Schor; Details: Professor Stacy Wolf will introduce Professor Esther Schor, who will introduce and have a conversation with the artist Deborah Kass, who will be showing slides of and speaking about her work.; Run Time: 1:27:16
  - Beating Hearts, 2016 November 16; Princeton University. University Center for Human Values; 1 digital file (Item 3627D)
    Speakers:Peter Singer, Charles Camosy, Karen Swallow Prior, Michael Dorf, Sherry Colb; Details: http://uchv.princeton.edu/events/ira-w-decamp-bioethics-seminar-beating-hearts-abortion-and-animal-rights; Run Time: 1:45:53
  - Doll Interview on Religion and Money, 2016 November 30; Center for the Study of Religion; 1 digital file (Item 3628D)
    Speakers:Mike Ullman and David Miller; Details: http://csr.princeton.edu/events/doll-myron-ullman/; Run Time: 1:07:58